export const questions=[
    {
        id:"1",
        question:"How to use Cashbook App?",
        answer:"1- CashBook is expense management app where a business keeps track of its earnings and expenses of money and that is used for various other reasons in a financial year on monthly, weekly and daily basis. \n 2- Create multiple Business profiles if you have multiple Businesses and among those profiles, you can create multiple cashbooks for Business or other purposes.\n3- Create Payment Modes, and tag them with your entries to know exactly how much amount did you receive or pay by using different modes of payment eg Cash, Google Pay, Net banking, etc. \n4- With the help of a Category, you can track how much you spent or earned on a particular purpose. E.g. Sales, purchase, transportation, salary, wages, etc.\n 5- Also, add a party with your entry for reference. It can be selected from your device's contact list or added manually. With the help of this option, you can send SMS and Bill/Invoice to the party.\n6- Create Business Team, and being an owner you can add Partners (if any) and other staff members to the team. Additionally, each staff member can be assigned a role as an Admin, Data Operator, or Viewer.\n7-CashBook does not involve any real transactions and money cannot be transferred. It is only for noting down your transactions to keep track of your expenses and earnings.\n8- Monitor and manage all your online bank transactions using the Bank Passbook.",
        similar_ques:[2,3,4,5],
        category:"Basics"
    },
    {
        id:"2",
        question:"How to do backdated entries?",
        answer:"Step 1. Tap on Cash-In or Cash-Out button\nStep 2 - Tap on Date field at the top to choose any date. from the past.\nStep 3 - Add amount, remark, category, payment mode & image if required.\nNote: If you are adding multiple entries on the same date use Save & Add new by using this you won't have to select the date for every entry.",
        similar_ques:[3,4,5,6],
        category:"Basics"

    },
    {
        id:"3",
        question:"How to View daily or monthly data in a book?",
        answer:"Step 1: Open the Book for which you want to see the Daily or Monthly Data.\nStep 2: Tap on the 'Select Date' option on the filter panel.\nStep 3: Choose the required option from the list.\nNote: For Daily or for a particular day data you can choose options; Today, Yesterday, Single day.However For Monthly data, you can choose option; This month, Last month, or option to select a particular month range.\nStep 4: After making the selection Tap on Apply.\nStep 5: To remove filter Tap on the 'Filter Icon' and Tap on 'Clear All",
        similar_ques:[4,5,6,7],
        category:"Basics",
    },
    {
        id:"4",
        question:"Is my data safe & backend up?",
        answer:"Your Phone data is absolutely safe ,backed up and linked with your phone number.whenever ypu login into any other phone using the same number you will get all your data",
        similar_ques:[5,6,7,8],
        category:"Backup"
    },
    {
        id:"5",
        question:"How to recover my data if i change or lose my phone?",
        answer:"All you need to do is login with same number you use cashbook from. Once you Login into any device you will get all your results",
        similar_ques:[6,7,8,9],
        category:"Back Up"
    },
    {
        id:"6",
        question:"What is Passbook?",
        answer:"Passbook lets you to tracl all your income/expenses automatically via your SMS transactions",
        similar_ques:[7,8,9,10],
        category:"Passbook"
    },
    {
        id:"7",
        question:"What is the benefits of using passbook?",
        answer:"PassBook makes adding entries much easier. Now you don't have to manage online entries separately, it gets synced automatically by your transactional text messages and displayed under the PassBook section.. And after that you can copy the transaction as an entry and tranfer it to the relevant Book.",
        similar_ques:[8,9,10,1],
        category:"Passbook"
    },
    {
        id:"8",
        question:"What is Business Profile?",
        answer:"Cashbook's Business Profile is an exclusive space. to set up businesses created specifically for shops, enterprises, and various business owners. With a custom business profile, the books of each specific business can be managed together in one place. A business owner can add all of their Partner and Staffs to their business team and manage their access. If someone owns multiple businesses then they can create multiple business profiles.\nWhile the app is primarily for business owners, it will not affect anyone if they are not using it for business purposes. It will direct you to the personal business space with all the books organized there. And from the Business profile, all the books can be accessed. One can also create multiple business profiles and keep their business & personal books in separate profiles",
        similar_ques:[9,10,1,2],
        category:"Business Profile"
    },
    {
        id:"9",
        question:"How to use Search?",
        answer:"You can search by remark and amount both\nStep 1-Open the book you want to search in.\nStep 2 - Tap on the search bar to start typing remark or amount.\nStep 3- If entries are found in both remark and amount then you can choose to see results from either remark or amount using tab bar below search bar.\nYou can also use the search screen to customise your search with filters, use recent searches to look up items, etc.",
        similar_ques:[10,1,2,3],
        category:"Search"
    },

    {
        id:"10",
        question:"Benefits of using category and payment Mode.",
        answer:"To know how much did you spend or earn on a particular item e.g. Food, Fuel etc, create a Category and tag it with your entries.\nYou can create Payment Modes and tag them with your entries to know exactly how much amount did you receive or pay by using different modes of payment eg Cash, Google Pay, Net banking etc",
        similar_ques:[10,1,2,3],
        category:"Entry Field"
    },


    
    



] 